https://stitchylizard.com/privacy-policy

Get in touch
Embroidery, Screen Printing & Promotional Products!CAD Stitchy LizardHomeAll Products ApparelT-ShirtsSweatshirtsGolf ShirtsJacketsDress ShirtsWorkwearAprons & Chef Uniforms
Sports UniformsHockeyBaseballBasketballFootballVolleyballCurlingSoccerLacrosseRugbyCyclingYogaBowling
HeadwearBaseball HatsTrucker HatsFlat BrimMiscellaneousWinter Hats
BagsBackpacksTote BagsBriefcasesMessenger BagsSports BagsLunch / Cooler BagsDrawstring BagsLaptop BagsLaundry BagsMiscellaneousShoe BagMakeup / Cosmetic
DrinkwareWater BottlesTravel MugsMugsThermosGlasswarePaper / PlasticCupsGift SetsMiscellaneousTumblersPromotional A - LAir FreshenersAutomotiveAwardsBalloonsBallsBBQ SetsBeltsBindersBlanketsBottle OpenersBraceletsBusiness Card HoldersButtonsCalculatorsCalendarsCandlesCandies & ChocolatesCarabinersChairsClocksCoastersCoinsColoring BooksComputer AccessoriesCoolersCrayonsCrestsDesktop AccessoriesDog TagsFirst Aid KitsFlagsFlashlightsFood ContainersFood / EdiblesFrisbeesGamesGardeningGlovesGolf AccessoriesHealth and BeautyHighlightersHousehold ItemsHunting & FishingKey ChainsLabels & StickersLanyardsLapel PinsLicense Plate FramesLightersLuggage TagsPromotional M - ZMagnetsMarkersMatchesMatsMedalsMouse PadsNail FilesName BadgesNapkinsOrnamentsPaper ProductsPatchesPatio UmbrellasPedometersPencilsPensPet AccessoriesPhone AccessoriesPicture FramesPillow CasesPlaying CardsPonchosRibbonsRubber BandsSewing KitsShoe LacesSocksSpa AccessoriesSpeakers & HeadsetsSports AccessoriesStickers & LabelsStress BallsSunglassesSwimming capsTablecloths & TowelsTape MeasureTelephone AccessoriesTentsTools & KnivesTooth BrushesTowelsTemporary TattoosTies & ScarvesTravel AccessoriesUmbrellasUSB SticksWatchesWine AccessoriesWristbandsWriting PadsWriting ToolsYoga AccessoriesPromo Marketing LabsAbout UsContact UsGet DirectionsAbout The CompanyHall of FameSatisfied CustomersCommunity ServiceNews / BlogGeneral InfoEmbroideryScreen PrintingDigitizingTackle Twill CategoriesCOVID-19Face MasksCounter BarriersBandanasStickersOther ProductsApparelT-ShirtsSweatshirts/SweatersGolf ShirtsJacketsShirtsAprons & Chef CoatsWorkwearScrubs & Lab CoatsBathrobesSweatpants/ShortsSports UniformsHockeyBaseballBasketballBowlingFootballVolleyballCurlingSoccerLacrosseRugbyCyclingYogaBagsBackpacksTote BagsBriefcasesMessenger BagsSports / Duffel BagsLunch / Cooler BagsDrawstring BagsLaptop BagsLaundry BagsMiscellaneousShoe BagMakeup / CosmeticDrinkwareWater BottlesStainless SteelGlass BottlesTritan™ BottlesSpring Water BottlesOther BottlesTravel MugsMugsThermosGlasswarePaper / PlasticCupsGift SetsMiscellaneousTumblersHeadwearBaseball HatsTrucker HatsFlat BrimDad HatsWinter HatsScarvesBandanas & Face MasksMiscellaneous PromotionalPromotional A - CAir FreshenersAutomotiveAwardsBalloonsBallsBBQ SetsBeltsBindersBlanketsBottle OpenersBraceletsBusiness Card HoldersButtonsCalculatorsCalendarsCandlesCandies & ChocolatesCannabis AccessoriesCarabinersChairsClocksCoastersCoinsColoring BooksComputer AccessoriesCoolersCovid ProductsCrayonsPromotional D - LDesktop AccessoriesDog TagsExercise & FitnessFirst Aid KitsFlagsFlashlightsFood ContainersFood / EdiblesFrisbeesGamesGardeningGlovesGolf AccessoriesHealth and BeautyCombs & BrushesCovid ProductsDentalManicure SetsHand SanitizersHand WarmersHot/Cold PacksMirrorsMoisturizing CreamsNail FilesTissue PacksSoapsHighlightersHousehold ItemsHunting & FishingKey ChainsLabels & StickersLanyards & Add-OnsLapel PinsLicense Plate FramesLightersLuggage TagsPromotional M - RMagnetsMarkersMatsMedalsMouse PadsNail FilesName BadgesNapkinsOrnamentsPaper ProductsPatches & CrestsPatio UmbrellasPedometersPencilsPensPet AccessoriesPhone AccessoriesPicture FramesPillow CasesPlaying CardsPonchosRibbonsRubber BandsPromotional S - ZSewing KitsShoe LacesSocksSpa AccessoriesSpeakers & HeadsetsSports AccessoriesStickers & LabelsPaper StickersVinyl StickersFabric LabelsStrawsStress BallsSunglassesSwimming capsTablecloths & TowelsTape MeasureTelephone AccessoriesTentsTools & KnivesTooth BrushesTowelsTemporary TattoosTies & ScarvesTravel AccessoriesUmbrellasUSB SticksWatchesWine AccessoriesWristbandsWriting PadsWriting ToolsYoga AccessoriesPrintBusiness Cardshidden(416) 203 7776 emb@stitchylizard.com
All Products COVID-19Face MasksCounter BarriersBandanasStickersOther ProductsApparelT-ShirtsSweatshirts/SweatersGolf ShirtsJacketsShirtsAprons & Chef CoatsWorkwearScrubs & Lab CoatsBathrobesSweatpants/ShortsSports UniformsHockeyBaseballBasketballBowlingFootballVolleyballCurlingSoccerLacrosseRugbyCyclingYogaBagsBackpacksTote BagsBriefcasesMessenger BagsSports / Duffel BagsLunch / Cooler BagsDrawstring BagsLaptop BagsLaundry BagsMiscellaneousShoe BagMakeup / CosmeticDrinkwareWater BottlesStainless SteelGlass BottlesTritan™ BottlesSpring Water BottlesOther BottlesTravel MugsMugsThermosGlasswarePaper / PlasticCupsGift SetsMiscellaneousTumblersHeadwearBaseball HatsTrucker HatsFlat BrimDad HatsWinter HatsScarvesBandanas & Face MasksMiscellaneous PromotionalPromotional A - CAir FreshenersAutomotiveAwardsBalloonsBallsBBQ SetsBeltsBindersBlanketsBottle OpenersBraceletsBusiness Card HoldersButtonsCalculatorsCalendarsCandlesCandies & ChocolatesCannabis AccessoriesCarabinersChairsClocksCoastersCoinsColoring BooksComputer AccessoriesCoolersCovid ProductsCrayonsPromotional D - LDesktop AccessoriesDog TagsExercise & FitnessFirst Aid KitsFlagsFlashlightsFood ContainersFood / EdiblesFrisbeesGamesGardeningGlovesGolf AccessoriesHealth and BeautyCombs & BrushesCovid ProductsDentalManicure SetsHand SanitizersHand WarmersHot/Cold PacksMirrorsMoisturizing CreamsNail FilesTissue PacksSoapsHighlightersHousehold ItemsHunting & FishingKey ChainsLabels & StickersLanyards & Add-OnsLapel PinsLicense Plate FramesLightersLuggage TagsPromotional M - RMagnetsMarkersMatsMedalsMouse PadsNail FilesName BadgesNapkinsOrnamentsPaper ProductsPatches & CrestsPatio UmbrellasPedometersPencilsPensPet AccessoriesPhone AccessoriesPicture FramesPillow CasesPlaying CardsPonchosRibbonsRubber BandsPromotional S - ZSewing KitsShoe LacesSocksSpa AccessoriesSpeakers & HeadsetsSports AccessoriesStickers & LabelsPaper StickersVinyl StickersFabric LabelsStrawsStress BallsSunglassesSwimming capsTablecloths & TowelsTape MeasureTelephone AccessoriesTentsTools & KnivesTooth BrushesTowelsTemporary TattoosTies & ScarvesTravel AccessoriesUmbrellasUSB SticksWatchesWine AccessoriesWristbandsWriting PadsWriting ToolsYoga AccessoriesPrintBusiness Cards
All CategoriesCOVID-19ApparelSports UniformsBagsDrinkwareHeadwearPromotionalPrint
0
$0.00You have no items in your shopping cart. Home Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyLast updated: November 15, 2016Stitchy Lizard ("us", "we", or "our") operates the www.stitchylizard.com website (the "Service").Personal Information Collect, Use, Disclosure and ConsentPersonal Information may include your name, email address, home address, phone number.We are committed to providing our clients, customers, members ("you", "your" or "them") with exceptional service. Providing exceptional service may involve the collection, use and, at times, the disclosure of your Personal Information. Protecting your Personal Information is one of our highest priorities. While we have always respected your privacy and safeguarded all Personal Information, we have strengthened our commitment to this goal. This is to continue to provide exceptional service to you and to comply with all laws regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information. We will inform you of why and how we collect, use and disclose Personal Information; obtain your consent, as required; and handle Personal Information according to applicable law. Our privacy commitment includes ensuring the accuracy, confidentiality, and security of your Personal Information and allowing you to request access to, and correction of, your personal information.This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.We will only collect Personal Information that is necessary to fulfill the following purposes:To verify identity;To identify your preferences;To open and manage an account;To ensure you receive a high standard of service;To meet regulatory requirements;Other legal reasons as apply to the goods and services requested.We will obtain your consent to collect, use or disclose Personal Information. In some cases, we can do so without your consent (see below). You can provide consent orally, in writing, electronically or through an authorized representative.You provide implied consent where our purpose for collecting using or disclosing your Personal Information would be considered obvious or reasonable in the circumstances. Consent may also be implied where you have notice and a reasonable opportunity to opt-out of having your Personal Information used for mail-outs, marketing or fundraising and you do not opt-out.We may collect, use or disclose Personal Information without the consent:When permitted or required by law;In an emergency that threatens an individual's life, health, or personal security;When the Personal Information is available from a public source;When we require legal advice from a lawyer;For the purposes of collecting a debt or protection from fraud;Other legally established reasons.We will not sell your Personal Information to other parties unless consent has been provided or implied. We retain your Personal Information for the time necessary to fulfill the identified purposes or a legal or business purpose. We will make reasonable efforts to ensure that your Personal Information is accurate and complete. You may request correction to your Personal Information to ensure its accuracy and completeness. A request must be in writing and provide sufficient detail to identify your Personal Information and the correction being sought.We are committed to ensuring the security of your Personal Information and may use passwords, encryption, firewalls, restricted employee access or other methods, in our discretion. We will use appropriate security measures when destroying your Personal Information such as shredding documents or deleting electronically stored information, at our discretion.Log DataWe may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this type of information in order to increase our Service's functionality. These third party service providers have their own privacy policies addressing how they use such information.CookiesCookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive.We use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service. If you do not instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent, your consent to our use of your Personal Information may be implied.Behavioral RemarketingStitchy Lizard uses remarketing services to advertise on third party web sites to you after you visited our Service. We, and our third party vendors, use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Service. In certain circumstances, your implied consent to our accessing, using or disclosing may be provided if you do not instruct your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is sent or if you do not opt out of Google Analytics or other services, as indicated below. We may use other social media platforms from time to time, a couple examples of Google and Facebook follow:GoogleGoogle AdWords remarketing service is provided by Google Inc.You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: http://www.google.com/settings/adsGoogle also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on - https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout - for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics.For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/FacebookFacebook remarketing service is provided by Facebook Inc.You can learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook by visiting this page: https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950To opt-out from Facebook's interest-based ads follow these instructions from Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/about/ads/#568137493302217Facebook adheres the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising established by the Digital Advertising Alliance. You can also opt-out from Facebook and other participating companies through the Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA http://www.aboutads.info/choices/, the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada in Canada http://youradchoices.ca/ or the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/, or opt-out using your mobile device settings.For more information on the privacy practices of Facebook, please visit Facebook's Data Policy: https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanationService ProvidersWe may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.CommunicationsWe may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.SecurityThe security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.International TransferYour information, including Personal Information, may be transferred to - and maintained on - computers located outside of your province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.If you are located outside Canada and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the information, including Personal Information, to Canada and process it there.Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.Links To Other SitesOur Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.Children's PrivacyOur Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 ("Minor").We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from Minors. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Minor has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Information from Minors without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.Changes To This Privacy PolicyWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at - emb@stitchylizard.com
COVID-19 ALERT:
Stitchy Lizard is NOW OPEN for business. If you need to pick up an order, please contact us to make arrangements ahead of time. Learn more. X
hiddenhiddenGot questions? Call Stitchy! (416) 203 7776Contact info41 Industrial Street - Unit 105 Toronto, ON - M4G 0C7TEL: (416) 203-7776FAX: (416) 203-7765Find it fastT-Shirts & ApparelSports UniformsHeadwearDrinkwareBags & KnapsacksPromotional ProductsPrint Services Customer careGet DirectionsAbout UsSatisfied CustomersContact Us
Proudly Canadian!
Back to TopStitchy Lizard Copyright ©
2002 - 2020Toronto, Ontario Canada. A promotional product company | 41 Industrial Street - Unit 105 Toronto, ON - M4G 0C7 TEL: (416) 203-7776, FAX: (416) 203-7765 Privacy Policy
